Associated American Artists
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Client Files, circa 1958-1980, Series 3:; (Box 29-48; 19 linear feet)
  - Ruboy, Jordan Dr. (Box 42)
  - Rus-Rz, (3 folders) (Box 42)
  - Ruttenberg, Harold J. (Box 42)
  - Saa, (2 folders) (Box 43)
  - Sal-Sandberg, (2 folders) (Box 43)
  - Sanders-Saz, (2 folders) (Box 43)
  - Sca-Sche, (2 folders) (Box 43)
  - Schi-Schm, (2 folders) (Box 43)
  - Schneider, Harold E. (Box 43)
  - Schn-Scho, (2 folders) (Box 43)
  - Schr-Schu, (2 folders) (Box 43)
  - Schwa-Schz, (2 folders) (Box 43)
  - Scollin, Dr. E.A. (Box 43)
  - Sco-Sei, (2 folders) (Box 43)
  - Sel-Ser, (3 folders) (Box 44)
  - Ses-Sez, (2 folders) (Box 44)
  - Sham-Shel, (3 folders) (Box 44)
  - Shem-Shi, (2 folders) (Box 44)
  - Sho-Sie, (2 folders) (Box 44)
  - Shohet, Ruben (Box 44)
  - Shute, John (Box 44)
  - Sig-Sil, (2 folders) (Box 44)
  - Sim-Sinf, (2 folders) (Box 44)
  - Sing-Sl, (2 folders) (Box 44)
  - Sma-Smi, (2 folders) (Box 44)
  - Smith, (2 folders) (Box 45)
  - Smo-Som, (2 folders) (Box 45)
  - Son-Spe, (2 folders) (Box 45)
  - Spi-Squ (Box 45)
  - Stam (Box 45)
  - Stan, (2 folders) (Box 45)
  - Stead (Box 45)
  - Steinberg (Box 45)
  - Stern (Box 45)
  - Sti (Box 45)
  - Stone, (2 folders) (Box 45)
  - Strp, (2 folders) (Box 45)
  - Sum, (2 folders) (Box 45)
  - Tab (Box 46)
  - Tabrisky, Joseph (Box 46)
  - Tal (Box 46)
  - Tas (Box 46)
  - Taylor, Martin A. (Box 46)
  - Te, (3 folders) (Box 46)
  - Tho, (2 folders) (Box 46)
  - Thr (Box 46)
  - To, (2 folders) (Box 46)
  - Tr, (2 folders) (Box 46)
  - Tu, (2 folders) (Box 46)
  - Tucker, Girard P. (Box 46)
  - U (Box 46)
  - V, (2 folders) (Box 46)
  - Wac-Wag (Box 46)
  - Wal-Waq, (2 folders) (Box 47)
  - War, (2 folders) (Box 47)
  - Wea (Box 47)
  - Wei, (2 folders) (Box 47)
  - Weir (Box 47)
  - Wej, (2 folders) (Box 47)
  - Wel, (2 folders) (Box 47)
  - Wha, (2 folders) (Box 47)
  - Wil, (3 folders) (Box 47)
  - Wim, (3 folders) (Box 47)
  - Woa (Box 47)
  - Wom, (3 folders) (Box 48)
  - Y (Box 48)
  - Z, (3 folders) (Box 48)
- Business Correspondence, 1959-1980, Series 4:; (Box 48-49; 2 linear feet)
  - Business Correspondence, 1959 (Box 48)
  - Business Correspondence, 1960 (Box 48)
  - Business Correspondence, 1961 (Box 48)
  - Business Correspondence, Jan-Mar 1962 (Box 48)
  - Business Correspondence, Apr-Dec 1962 (Box 48)
  - Business Correspondence, Jan-Jul 1963 (Box 48)
  - Business Correspondence, Aug-Dec 1963 (Box 48)
  - Business Correspondence, Jan-Mar 1964 (Box 48)
  - Business Correspondence, Apr-Jun 1964 (Box 48)
  - Business Correspondence, Jul-Sep 1964 (Box 48)
  - Business Correspondence, Oct-Dec 1964 (Box 48)
  - Business Correspondence, Jan-Mar 1965 (Box 48)
  - Business Correspondence, Apr-Jun 1965 (Box 48)
  - Business Correspondence, Jul-Sep 1965 (Box 48)
  - Business Correspondence, Oct-Dec 1965 (Box 48)
  - Business Correspondence, Jan-Feb 1966 (Box 48)
  - Business Correspondence, Mar-Apr 1966 (Box 48)
  - Business Correspondence, May-Jun 1966 (Box 48)
  - Business Correspondence, Jul-Aug 1966 (Box 48)
  - Business Correspondence, Sep-Oct 1966 (Box 48)
  - Business Correspondence, Nov-Dec 1966 (Box 48)
  - Business Correspondence, Jan-Feb 1967 (Box 48)
  - Business Correspondence, Mar-Apr 1967 (Box 48)
  - Business Correspondence, May-Jun 1967 (Box 48)
  - Business Correspondence, Jul-Aug 1967 (Box 48)
  - Business Correspondence, Sep-Oct 1967 (Box 48)
  - Business Correspondence, Nov-Dec 1967 (Box 48)
  - Business Correspondence, Jan-Feb 1968 (Box 48)
  - Business Correspondence, Feb-Apr 1968 (Box 48)
  - Business Correspondence, May-Jun 1968 (Box 48)
  - Business Correspondence, Jul-Aug 1968 (Box 48)
  - Business Correspondence, Sep-Oct 1968 (Box 49)
  - Business Correspondence, Nov-Dec 1968 (Box 49)
  - Business Correspondence, Jan-Feb 1969 (Box 49)
  - Business Correspondence, Mar-May 1969 (Box 49)
  - Business Correspondence, May-Jun 1969 (Box 49)
  - Business Correspondence, Jul-Aug 1969 (Box 49)
  - Business Correspondence, Sep-Oct 1969 (Box 49)
  - Business Correspondence, Nov-Dec 1969 (Box 49)
  - Business Correspondence, Jan-Feb 1970 (Box 49)
  - Business Correspondence, Mar-Apr 1970 (Box 49)
  - Business Correspondence, May-Jun 1970 (Box 49)
  - Business Correspondence, Jul-Aug 1970 (Box 49)
  - Business Correspondence, Sep-Oct 1970 (Box 49)
  - Business Correspondence, Nov-Dec 1970 (Box 49)
  - Business Correspondence, Jan-Feb 1971 (Box 49)
  - Business Correspondence, Mar- Apr 1971 (Box 49)
  - Business Correspondence, May-Jun 1971 (Box 49)
  - Business Correspondence, Jul-Aug 1971 (Box 49)
  - Business Correspondence, Sep-Oct 1971 (Box 49)
  - Business Correspondence, Nov-Dec 1971 (Box 49)
  - Business Correspondence, Jan-Feb 1972 (Box 49)
  - Business Correspondence, Mar-Apr 1972 (Box 49)
  - Business Correspondence, May-Jun 1972 (Box 49)
  - Business Correspondence, Jul-Sep 1972 (Box 49)
  - Business Correspondence, Sep-Oct 1972 (Box 49)
  - Business Correspondence, Nov-Dec 1972 (Box 49)
  - Business Correspondence, Jan-Feb 1973 (Box 49)
  - Business Correspondence, Feb-Apr 1973 (Box 49)
  - Business Correspondence, May-Jun 1973 (Box 49)
  - Business Correspondence, Jul-Aug 1973 (Box 49)
  - Business Correspondence, Sep-Oct 1973 (Box 49)
  - Business Correspondence, Nov-Dec 1973 (Box 49)
  - Business Correspondence, Jan-Feb 1974 (Box 49)
  - Business Correspondence, Mar-Jun 1974 (Box 49)
  - Business Correspondence, Jul-Aug 1974 (Box 49)
  - Business Correspondence, Sep-Dec 1974 (Box 49)
  - Business Correspondence, Jan-Mar 1975 (Box 49)
  - Business Correspondence, Apr-June 1975 (Box 49)
  - Business Correspondence, Jul-Oct 1975 (Box 49)
  - Business Correspondence, Nov-Dec 1975 (Box 49)
  - Business Correspondence, 1976 (Box 49)
  - Business Correspondence, 1977 (Box 49)
  - Business Correspondence, 1978 (Box 49)
  - Business Correspondence, 1979 (Box 49)
  - Business Correspondence, 1980 (Box 49)
  - Business Correspondence, Undated (Box 49)
- Financial Records, 1960-1981, Series 5:; (Box 50-51; 1 linear feet)
  - Financial Records, 1960 (Box 50)
  - Financial Records, 1961 (Box 50)
  - Financial Records, 1962 (Box 50)
  - Financial Records, 1963 (Box 50)
  - Financial Records, 1964 (Box 50)
  - Financial Records, 1965 (Box 50)
  - Financial Records, Jan-Jun 1966 (Box 50)
  - Financial Records, Jul-Dec 1966 (Box 50)
  - Financial Records, Jan-Jun 1967 (Box 50)
  - Financial Records, Jul-Dec 1967 (Box 50)
  - Financial Records, Jan-Jun 1968 (Box 50)
  - Financial Records, 1968 (Box 50)
  - Financial Records, Jul-Dec 1968 (Box 50)
  - Financial Records, Jan-Apr 1969 (Box 50)
  - Financial Records, May-Aug 1969 (Box 50)
  - Financial Records, Sep-Dec 1969 (Box 50)
  - Financial Records, Jan-Apr 1970 (Box 50)
  - Financial Records, May-Aug 1970 (Box 50)
  - Financial Records, Sep-Dec 1970 (Box 50)
  - Financial Records, Jan-Apr 1971 (Box 50)
  - Financial Records, May-Aug 1971 (Box 50)
  - Financial Records, Sep-Dec 1971 (Box 50)
  - Financial Records, Jan-Apr 1972 (Box 50)
  - Financial Records, May-Aug 1972 (Box 50)
  - Financial Records, Sep-Dec 1972 (Box 50)
  - Financial Records, Jan-Jun 1973 (Box 50)
  - Financial Records, Jul-Dec 1973 (Box 50)
  - Financial Records, 1974 (Box 51)
  - Financial Records, 1975 (Box 51)
  - Financial Records, 1976 (Box 51)
  - Financial Records, 1977 (Box 51)
  - Financial Records, 1978 (Box 51)
  - Financial Records, 1979 (Box 51)
  - Financial Records, 1981 (Box 51)
- Sales Catalogs, 1955-1979, Series 6:; (Box 51-53; 2 linear feet)
  - Sales Catalogs, 1955-1958 (Box 51)
  - Sales Catalogs, 1959-1963 (Box 51)
  - Sales Catalogs, 1964 (Box 51)
  - Sales Catalogs, 1966, (2 folders) (Box 51)
  - Sales Catalogs, 1967, (3 folders) (Box 51)
  - Sales Catalogs, 1968 (Box 51)
  - Sales Catalogs, 1969 (Box 51)
  - Sales Catalogs, 1970 (Box 51)
  - Sales Catalogs, 1971-1972 (Box 51)
  - Sales Catalogs, 1972 (Box 51)
  - Sales Catalogs, 1973, (2 folders) (Box 52)
  - Sales Catalogs, 1974, (3 folders) (Box 52)
  - Sales Catalogs, 1975, (4 folders) (Box 52)
  - Sales Catalogs, 1976, (3 folders) (Box 52)
  - Sales Catalogs, 1977, (1, 2 of 5 folders) (Box 52)
  - Sales Catalogs, 1977, (3, 4, 5 of 5 folders) (Box 53)
  - Sales Catalogs, 1978, (3 folders) (Box 53)
  - Sales Catalogs, 1979 (Box 53)
  - Sales Catalogs: German, Unknown Date, (2 folders) (Box 53)
  - Sales Catalogs: French, Unknown Date, (4 folders) (Box 53)
  - Sales Catalogs: Italian, Spanish, Asian, Unknown Date (Box 53)
  - Sales Catalogs: English, Unknown Date, (5 folders) (Box 53)
- Exhibition Catalogs, 1950-1978, Series 7:; (Box 54; 1 linear foot)
  - Exhibition Catalogs, 1950-1960 (Box 54)
  - Exhibition Catalogs, 1961-1963 (Box 54)
  - Exhibition Catalogs, 1964-1965 (Box 54)
  - Exhibition Catalogs, 1966 (Box 54)
  - Exhibition Catalogs, 1967 (Box 54)
  - Exhibition Catalogs, 1968 (Box 54)
  - Exhibition Catalogs, 1969, (2 folders) (Box 54)
  - Exhibition Catalogs, 1970 (Box 54)
  - Exhibition Catalogs, 1971 (Box 54)
  - Exhibition Catalogs, 1972 (Box 54)
  - Exhibition Catalogs, 1973 (Box 54)
  - Exhibition Catalogs, 1974 (Box 54)
  - Exhibition Catalogs, 1975, (2 folders) (Box 54)
  - Exhibition Catalogs, 1976, (2 folders) (Box 54)
  - Exhibition Catalogs, 1977 (Box 54)
  - Exhibition Catalogs, 1978, (2 folders) (Box 54)
  - Exhibition Catalogs, Unknown Date (Box 54)
- Scrapbooks, 1958-1980, Series 8:; (Box 55-57; 0.9 linear feet)
  - Scrapbooks Nos. 1-4, 1958-1967 (Box 55 (sol))
  - Scrapbooks Nos. 5-9, 1968-1974 (Box 56 (sol))
  - Scrapbooks Nos. 10-13,1975-1980 (Box 57 (sol))
- Posters, circa 1960s-1970s, Series 9:
  - Oversized Posters (Box OV 58)